你們覺得我應該給崔維斯
Okay, what do you think I should get Travis
什么樣的畢業禮物
for his graduation gift --
吸塵機器人  電動車
the robot vacuum, uh, electric bike,
還是單人氣墊船
or a one-person hovercraft?
絕對不要吸塵機器人
Definitely not a robot vacuum.
我最怕那種東西了
Those things really creep me out.
我的吸塵器得要有靈魂才行
I need my vacuums to have soul.
他還有四個月才畢業呢
He doesn't graduate for four months.
我以為你要減少提前購物呢
I thought you agreed to cut back on your early shopping?
好吧
Okay, fine.
我退幾樣總行了吧
Then I'll just make some returns,
那樣的話你就永遠不會知道
and you'll never know what you were getting
2015年圣誕我要送什么給你
for christmas 2015.
美黑噴霧套裝
A spray tan package!
還不如買個按摩椅呢
Oh, hey, why don't you get him this massage chair?
如果你想被撫摸
"Perfect for those times you wanna be touched,
卻又孤零零  最佳選擇
but you're all alone."
你可以讓他們直接送貨到他的房間
You can have them deliver it right to his room upstairs,
反正他還要住十年呢
where he'll be for the next ten years.
崔維斯畢業了當然就不在家里住了呀
Why would Travis be living here after graduation?
但是他上的是藝術學校啊
'Cause he's graduating from art school.
拜托  艾莉
Oh, come on, Ellie.
我們都知道崔維是個有理想  很獨立
Now we all know that Trav is ambitious, independent,
而且很有藝術天分的孩子
and has a fantastic work ethic.
笑什么啊
Why are we laughing?
■
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
■
翻譯：木淺薰  薩薩  吃貨丁小七
熟女鎮
第五季 第七集
翻譯：沐頭  Hannah  愛天津
剛還說到你呢
Hey, I was just talking about you.
再有幾個月就畢業了吧
So graduation's in a couple months, huh?
好像是的
Yeah. Guess that's right.
校對：TanKnoX          總監   蘋果果
得過八九年  你的藝術文憑
In the eight or nine years it'll take you
才會幫你賺到錢
to find a way to make money with an art degree,
后期：銘哥騎白馬       時間軸：信徒
在此期間  你想干什么
What do you see yourself doing?
不管是地雷陣還是萬丈深淵
Lotta irons in the fire.
我都將一往無前
Can't wait to, uh, dive in,
義無反顧  旗開得勝
get my hands dirty, really hit the ground running.
要去上課了  回見
I gotta go to class. Later.
拜  寶貝
Bye, babe.
聽起來崔維斯挺忙的
Well, it sounds like travis has got a lot going on.
那只是些大套話而已
Those are just empty buzzwords.
上班時要是我沒詞了
I do that at work
就會用這些
when I can't think of anything to say.
全面發展  重點培養
"You need to prioritize,"
重整旗鼓  抓住市場
"Refocus your capital," "Really attack the market."
你覺得我該重回市場嗎
Should I be attacking the market?
好  去吧
Yeah, go ahead.
我不介意男生玩玩偶
I don't mind dating a guy who plays with action figures,
我只是覺得不該我來為玩偶付錢
I just don't think I should have to pay for them.
男人需要的是工作
Dude needs a J-O-B.
我要走了
I should go.
我們正在嘗試勸斯坦加入避風灣學院
We are trying to get Stan into Gulfhaven Academy.
錄取部的那個女人要來家里呢
The woman from admissions is coming by the house.
那地方很搶手的
That place is crazy competitive.
都不怎么收人
They barely accept anyone.
跟我很像  只不過它是學校我是人
Like me, but a school.
你怎么不早點告訴我呢
Why didn't you tell me?
你知道我打溫莎領結很慢的
You know I need at least an hour to tie a windsor knot.
你不能來
You're not invited.
每次說道斯坦的未來你就眼淚汪汪的
You know you get all weepy talking about Stan's future,
總是讓自己出盡洋相
and then you make a huge ass of yourself.
我沒事的  我知道斯坦會長大
I'm cool with Stan getting older...
上學
going to school...
成為一個男子漢
becoming a man.
夠了  你管吧  茱爾斯  好運
Okay. All right, that's all yours, Jules. Enjoy.
發泄出來就好
Just let it out.
就好像昨天他還是個小嬰兒
It's like yesterday he was a baby!
勞里  茱爾斯呢
Laurie, where's Jules?
你還好吧
Whoa, are you okay?
都沒給我起難聽的外號
You didn't even call me a name.
我趕時間呢  侏儒婊
There's no time, trample-stiltskin.
好吧  其實也沒那么急  茱爾斯呢
Okay, there's a little time. Where is she?
她帶客人看房子呢
She's showing a house.
你不是要去參加面試嗎
Aren't you supposed to be at your interview?
我的保姆病了
My nanny is sick.
要是沒人看著斯坦
If I don't have someone watching Stan,
他又要把什么千島醬
he might put thousand island dressing
往我的洗發水里兌了
in my shampoo bottle again.
親愛的  我看著他就好了呀
Honey, I'll watch him.
我的15個寄養兄弟姐妹以前都是我帶的
I used to take care of my 15 foster sibs.
斯坦很難帶的
Well, stan is a major handful.
小婦人  拜托你
Bitch, please.
我有個弟弟以為他自己是只斗牛狗
One of my brothers thought he was a pit bull.
所以我就在狗玩具上抹上花生醬
I used to fill a dog toy with peanut butter
他就再也不亂咬了  我應付的了
to keep him from biting. I think I got this.
好吧  我實在太忙了
Okay, but only because I'm totally screwed.
快行動啊  肉夾饃
Come on, hooba-skank!
嘿  是我幫你的忙哎
Hey! I'm doing you a favor.
抱歉  條件反射
I'm sorry, it's reflex.
非常感謝你幫忙
Thank you so much for helping.
騷貨
Slut-bag.
鮑比  我們得談談
Bobby, we need to talk.
我想我知道你想談什么
Uh-oh. I know that voice.
不是崔維斯出事了
Either something's going on with Travis,
就是你姑姑格雷西又死了
or your aunt gracie died again.
我問崔維斯畢業后
I asked Travis what he wants to do
有什么打算
after graduation,
他說什么"一往無前"
and he said he has a lot of irons in the fire.
聽起來咱孩子要下海了
Sounds like our boy means business.
不是那樣的
No, he doesn't.
我知道他想當攝影師
I know he wants to be a photographer,
但是那不是一蹴而就的事
but that could take a really long time.
成功之前他靠什么生活呢
What's he gonna do for money until then?
很快   崔維就能
Pretty soon, Trav will be on his own...
獨當一面了
out in the world.
好吧  你先回避下行嗎
Okay, you're gonna have to go, dude.
你也要把我趕走嗎
You're kicking me out, too?!
真是的
Damn it.
我不想讓崔維斯成為那種
I don't want Travis to be one of those kids
畢業之后什么也不干
that finishes school, and just sits around
空談夢想的啃老族
doing nothing, waiting for his dream job.
我們該怎么辦
What are we gonna do?
你太溺愛他  他是沒法成長的
You hold him so close he never grows up.
-拜托  -我不說了
- Dude. - I'll stop.
我們得和他好好談談
We have to sit Travis down,
確保他有切實可行的計劃才行
and we have to make sure that he has a plan.
我加入
I'm in.
那還不起來
Hello?
現在就去嗎  好吧  走起
Hmm? Oh, you meant now. Oh, come on. Yep, got it.
看來你有滿腔苦水要吐
Looks like you're dealing with something.
所以我打算給你上杯啤酒然后走人
So I'm just gonna leave you with that and...
艾莉把我趕出家門了
Ellie kicked me out of the house,
我現在不知道該干嘛好
and I don't know what to do with myself.
你開玩笑的吧
Are you kidding?
在我第一次婚姻里
In my first marriage,
老婆沒空的時候
my friends and I would rage
我和朋友都會出去肆意猖獗
when our wives were busy.
我和一哥們曾經
Me and a buddy once
著名古巴歌手
闖入格洛麗亞·埃斯特凡家
broke into Gloria Estefan's house
然后和她的奶奶照了張相
And took a picture with her grammy.
不是格萊美獎杯
Not the award...
她奶奶正好在給她看家
Her grandmother was house-sitting.
我不知道
I don't know.
我可能只會穿條舒服的休閑褲
I might just put on my cozy pants
然后把機油換換
and get an oil change.
這樣吧  茱爾斯和崔維斯在一塊呢
Tell you what... Jules is with Travis,
所以我來幫你
So I'm gonna help you out.
我們可以做任何你想做的事
We're gonna do anything you want.
做些瘋狂的事  你說了算  基友日
Something crazy, you name it. Bro day!
一定要叫"基友日"嗎
Do we have to call it "Bro day"?
有同性戀里受方的意思
我以前管這叫"哥們瘋耍日"
Well, I used to call it "Dudes on the down low,"
但事實證明  這名字別有"內涵"
But turns out, that means something else.
斯坦的測試成績很好
Stan's test scores are great.
但我們希望招收的學生
But we're looking for kids from families
是來自于更為多樣化家庭的孩子
that are a little more... diverse.
斯坦有一半的古巴血統
Well, Stan's half-cuban.
這可是佛羅里達州  托瑞斯夫人
This is Florida, Mrs. Torres.
我敢說你隨便扔塊石頭都能砸到個古巴人
I dare you to throw a rock and not hit a cuban.
比喻而已  可別真扔啊
Figuratively.
抱歉  打擾你們了
Sorry, sorry to interrupt.
我只是來拿斯坦的故事書的
I just need to grab Stan's books.
很遺憾  我們只剩下幾個名額了
Unfortunately, we only have a few spots left.
我們希望能留給來自
And we hope to fill those with a child from say,
低收入或是單親家庭
a low-income bracket or single-parent home,
又或是另類家庭的孩子
or perhaps an alternative family.
抱歉  親愛的
Excuse me. Oh, baby girl.
你每次穿這毛衣都會讓我
You know I can't resist you
欲火焚身  難以自控
when you wear this sweater.
我沒想到你們居然是...
Oh, I didn't realize that you were...
是的  無比驕傲的蕾絲邊
Yes, big-time.
無比驕傲
Big-time.
快要畢業了  你很興奮吧
So this graduating thing is exciting.
我知道你有不少靠譜的計劃
And I know you have a lot of irons in the fire.
沒錯  你得廣撒大網
Yeah, you gotta cast a wide net,
以餌勾誘  看能釣著啥大魚
bait the hook, see what bites.
哥們  真像是干大事業的人
Mover and shaker, this guy.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我們都支持你的攝影事業
We both support your photography,
但這事業要起步可能得花上好幾年
But that could take years.
那事業起步前你打算做什么
So what are you planning to do in the meantime?
多著呢  拍個動畫網絡連續劇
A ton... cooking up an animated web series,
或是著手做個手機軟件玩玩
may kickstart an app.
美國主要的新聞網站  博客門戶網
如果我的博客能外聯到《赫芬頓郵報》官網上
and if my blog gets linked to Huffpo,
那哥的前途將無可限量
Sky's the limit.
什么雞  什么劍  什么報
All I heard was "Po," "Kick," And "App."
我換個方式問你吧
So let me ask you another way...
你要怎么養活自己呢
Um, how are you gonna support yourself?
搬回來住  等著我的創意大獲成功唄
Probably just move back here until one of my ideas pops.
我還想到了個真人秀題材的構思
Oh! And I thought of an idea for a reality show
講述古老的消防站的故事
About old firehouses.
我朋友的堂兄弟的鄰居是個制作人
My friend's cousin lives next to a producer.
所以  希望他愿意買賬了
So... fingers crossed.
好吧  咱們養了個游手好閑的啃老族
Yep, we raised a deadbeat.
小崔壓根沒想找份正經工作
Trav has no interest at a real job.
我20歲的時候  還洗過車呢
You know, when I was 20, I-I worked at a car wash.
我會辭職是因為那幫老頭不停嚷嚷
I mean, I only quit because all the old men were yelling,
"把咪咪壓在爺的車窗上"
"Put 'em on the glass!"
我們認識的時候  我還在一愛爾蘭酒吧
When we met, I was selling shoes
賣鞋呢
at an irish pub.
我從醉漢腳下把鞋偷走
I would steal them off the drunk guys
在打烊的時候再賣回給他們
and sell them back to 'em at the end of the night.
是啊  你跟我說這事的時候
Yeah, when you told me that,
我只想立馬嫁給你
there was no way I wasn't marrying you.
也許小崔能用金屬探測器
Hey, maybe Trav can use a metal detector
在海邊撿硬幣
and collect coins at the beach.
不對  如果沒錢怎么買得起
Now, well, how do you buy a metal detector
金屬探測器呢
when you have no money?
我沒主意了
I'm out of ideas.
是啊  我覺得崔維斯得找份
Yeah, I think Travis needs a job
更正經的工作
that's more... a job.
"新巴克"的經理可喜歡我了
The manager at Coffee Bucks loves me.
他讓我用擁抱來付咖啡錢
He lets me pay for coffee in hugs.
他應該愿意給崔維斯面試機會
I bet he'd give Travis a job interview.
真不敢相信你居然吻我
I cannot believe you kissed me!
什么親吻  你們接吻了嗎
What kiss? You kissed?
我怎么沒看見你們接吻
W-where was I when you kissed?
多大的事啊  又不是舌吻
Big deal. There was no tongue slip.
那是因為我緊閉著嘴  你才沒得逞
There was no tongue because I shut my lips.
我覺得你可想戳進來了
I felt you trying to poke in.
好了  馬上告訴我發生什么事了
Okay, I need to know what's going on right now.
軟糖·克萊森剛才在招生代表面前
Jelly Clarkson made out with me
調侃歌手凱莉·克萊森
強吻了我
in front of the admissions rep,
害人家以為我們是戀人
who now thinks we're lovers.
她說他們要招來自
She said that they were looking for kids
另類家庭的孩子
from alternative families.
同性戀家庭就是的啊
As in... same-sex couples.
好極了  她打來了
Oh, great. That's her now.
感覺如何  你...你喜歡嗎
What was it like? I mean... did you like it?
你覺得艾莉的吻技
I mean, do you think that Ellie would be
會比我厲害嗎
a better kisser than me?
我一直覺得我能當個超贊的基佬
I always thought I would make a magnificent gay man.
我既溫柔又開放  自由不羈
I'm a tender, open-minded, free spirit,
而且哥器大活好
And I got a quality unit.
斯坦在候選名單上排名很高
Well, Stan is now very high on their waiting list.
他們剛邀請我參加候選人家長野餐會
They just invited me to a prospective parent picnic.
群就說這招絕對管用吧
Boo-yah! I told you it would work.
這又有什么問題呢  煩人精
So what's the problem, lady?
問題是她想讓我
The problem is that she wants me
帶上我的伴侶出席
to bring my partner.
好吧  這的確是個問題
Oh. Yeah. That might be a problem.
天吶  瞧瞧咱們仨
Goodness, look at us.
三個好閨蜜  開懷大笑...
The best of friends just laughin'...
相愛
And lovin'...
相"親"
And kissing?
親  現在不要
Not now, sweetie.
基友時間  你都有什么好主意
Bro time! What do you got?
來看看
Okay, let's see.
展示我的貝殼收藏
Um, beef up my shell collection,
做水果奶昔
make some fruit smoothies.
要知道我一直想自己種羅勒草
You know, I always wanted to grow my own basil.
老兄  難得有機會放縱一把
Dude, you got a free pass here.
我們要做點狂拽酷炫的事
We gotta do something bro-dacious
比如開快艇  釣鯰魚
like jet-skiing, catfishing,
徒手沖浪  瘋狂摩托  洞穴探險
or body surfing, or motorcycling, spelunking,
大力扣籃或者酩酊大醉
or dunking and crunking!
聽到我感興趣的我會告訴你
I guess I'll know it when I hear it.
格雷森
Hey, Grayson?
我能借幾支裝飾雞尾酒那種小傘嗎
Could I borrow some of those tiny drink umbrellas?
小雪球和我要做一個"貓咪視頻"
Snowball and I are making a cat video.
貓咪視頻
Cat video!
不  不  不可以
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
你說我想做什么都可以的
You said anything I want,
我就想做這個  聽起來"喵"贊
And this is what I want. It sounds purr-fect.
喵了個咪的
Meow we're talkin'.
一定超有意思喵
It'll be kitty fun.
你居然能給小崔找到面試
Hey, it's pretty cool you got Trav an interview,
不過我懷疑他會發現我們偷聽的
but I doubt he's gonna dig us eavesdroppin'.
放心  我準備好掩護了
Please, I've got this covered.
崔維斯  告訴我
So, Travis, tell me...
你為什么想來新巴克咖啡店上班
why do you wanna work for coffee bucks?
其實我不是很想
Well, "want" is a bit of an overstatement.
是我媽逼我過來面試的
my mom forced me to take this interview.
你了解的
You know how it is.
給你點誠實分
Bonus points for honesty, I suppose.
你有什么長處嗎
Uh, what would you say are your strengths?
做點科幻小電影
Sci-fi movie trivia,
設計T恤  微妙地諷刺別人
ironic t-shirt ideas, subtle sarcastic put-downs--
順便說一句  你的領帶不錯
nice tie, by the way.
謝謝
Oh, thank you.
開場白不夠好
Not a strong start.
不過他還是有機會的
But he could still put it around.
你對咖啡充滿熱情吧
But you are passionate about coffee.
咖啡
Uh... coffee?
我對攝影充滿熱情
I'm passionate about photography,
對我女朋友充滿熱情
Passionate about my girlfriend.
是什么樣的怪咖才會對咖啡充滿熱情啊
What kind of weirdo is passionate about coffee?
我這個怪咖就對咖啡充滿熱情
This weirdo is passionate about coffee.
你可以走了
I think you should go.
我以后都不能"以抱代付"了
I might not be able to pay with hugs anymore.
沒什么會比夾著小公文包的
If there is anything funnier than a cat C.P.A.
貓會計師更有意思
with a tiny briefcase...
完全沒看出來
I don't know what it is.
要知道我上次基友時間
You know, on my last bro day,
跟我兄弟開著快艇
my buddy and I took a cigarette boat
到古巴去
to get cuban food...
吃了古巴菜
in cuba.
我得去弄點金槍魚
I should get some tuna.
小雪球肚子一餓
Snowball can get a little bratty
脾氣就會變得不好
If his blood sugar drops.
做喵會計應該會很辛苦
It's hard work being a cat-countant.
喵會計
A cat-countant?!
你們自己看不到是吧  瞧瞧你們
Can you not see yourselves? Look at you,
兩個成年男人試著給一只貓
You're two grown men trying to put a cat
打領結插鋼筆  傻不傻啊
in a bow tie and a pocket protector. It's so stupid.
至少讓它做些酷一點的事
You should at least make him something cool,
比如說
you know, like...
比如說調酒師什么的
You know, like a bartender or something.
你是說  調酒貓
You mean, cat-tender?
沒錯  比如說調酒貓
Yeah, like a-- like a cat-tender.
酒吧走起
To the pub!
我們最多假扮情侶到
Okay, we are only going along with this insanity
我想出辦法
until I find a way to straighten
證明自己是直的為止
this whole thing out.
在我們還是情侶期間
Okay, well, as long as we are a couple,
你需要做的有
my relationship demands are as follows--
不時的撫摸親吻
constant touching, surprise kisses,
偶爾襲胸  還要經常贊美我
casual boob grazes, and regular compliments.
重點關照我的眼睛頭發和腳
some good areas to focus on-- my eyes, hair, feet.
我不干了
I'm out.
托瑞斯太太  很高興見到你
Mrs. Torres, it's great to see you.
能跟我的伴侶一起過來真好
It's so nice to be here... with my partner.
我們都是彼此的摯愛
We are lovers, above all else.
沒錯吧  親
Isn't that right, lover?
是的  親
Yes, lover.
你的眼睛好像在說
Aw! You have that look in your eye,
你準備贊美我了
like you're about to pay me a compliment.
你真  真漂亮
You're... pretty,
尤其是頭發眼睛和腳的部分
Particularly in the hair, eye, and feet area.
見到這么相愛的伴侶真激動
It's inspiring to see a couple so in love.
我的手好像粘到她身上一樣
I can't keep my hands off her.
直接來到女士天堂
Aw. Highway to the lady zone.
是不
What-what?
沒錯
What-what, indeed.
我還以為不會落到這個地步的
You know, I was hoping it wouldn't come to this,
可是小崔現在沒有工作也沒有計劃
but Trav has no job, no plan,
還瞧不起金錢
and no respect for money.
得嚇嚇他了
It's time to scare him straight.
我就是那個最后一事無成的案例
And I am the poster boy for zero ambition--
住在一艘岸上的船里  勉強糊口
living on a land boat, hand-to-mouth,
拿一大袋"好市多"的小餅干當枕頭
and I use a costo-sized bag of oyster crackers as a pillow.
你怎么不卷條毛巾做枕頭
Why don't you just roll up a towel?
那我用什么墊在門下面
What would I put under the door
防止蛇鉆進來
to keep the snakes out?
發生什么事兒了  家長們
What's up, parental unit?
崔維斯  請坐
Travis, have a seat.
我給你講講我的人生吧
Let me tell you about my life, son.
我昨晚吃了六個多麗滋玉米卷
Last night I had six doritos locos tacos
然后在星光下裸體睡著了
and fell asleep naked under the stars,
因為我沒有工作
I got no job,
醒了以后也不知道去哪里
and nowhere to be when I wake up.
聽起來  超酷的
Sounds... amazing.
明明超悲催
It's awful.
要知道他居然從壽司店加油站里偷電
You know, he has to steal his electricity from a sushi restaurant/ gas station.
當然  如果他想找份工作的話
Of course, if he was willing to get a job,
他就不會這么苦逼了
He wouldn't be in this pathetic situation.
我不覺得那很苦逼
I don't know if it was pathetic.
是又苦逼又丟臉
It's pathetic and embarrassing.
你以后也會這樣
And that's what's gonna happen to you, boy.
你們是在搞什么恐嚇教育法嗎
Is this some type of "Scared straight" routine?
崔維斯  你該醒醒了
Travis, you need a wake-up call.
我不忍直視你昨天面試的樣子
I mean, I can't believe how you acted in that interview.
所以我面試的時候  你在監視我
So you were spying on me in the interview?
你就不能讓我自己做事情呢
Why can't you just let me do anything on my own?
對啊  茱爾斯  你為什么老管閑事
Yeah, Jules, why do you always have to meddle?
你在干嘛  我們是同一戰線的
What are you doing? We're a team.
我們本來是的  誰叫你對我落井下石
We were until you threw me under the bus.
對啊  但是我們就是應該一起
Yes, but we were supposed to throw you
對你落井下石啊
under the bus together.
你們瘋了嗎  我不玩了
This is crazy! I'm outta here.
對  我也不玩了
Yeah, you know what? I'm outta here, too.
那  我也走了
Well, I'm outta here, too!
該死  真不是摔門而出的好地方
Damn it! This is not an easy place to storm out of.
喝得好兇啊
Wow, really sucking it down, huh?
那又怎樣
Yeah, so what?
你的酒好難喝  你的餅干都過期了
Your wine is like crap, pretzels are stale.
那張傻兮兮的照片是怎么回事
What's that stupid photograph?
那是我和我兄弟布雷克
Oh, that's me and my buddy Blake
跟葛洛麗亞·伊斯特芬的奶奶
with Gloria Estefan's grammy.
80-90年代流行樂壇的頭號天后
好基友一輩子
We were being bro-dacious.
的確挺潮的
Well, that's actually kinda cool.
抱歉  親愛的  我只是...
I'm sorry, honey, I'm just--
我只是在糾結崔維斯的事情
I'm upset about this Travis thing.
而且鮑比把整個恐嚇教育法都毀了
And Bobby completely ruined our "Scared straight" routine.
那套完全沒用
That never works.
不過我可以把憤怒的囚犯模仿得很像
Although, I do do a great angry inmate.
小子  你不會想要來我的地盤
Boy, you don't wanna come into my world.
因為我會把草莓唇膏扔給你
I'll slap some strawberry lip gloss on you
讓你成為我的女人
and make you my woman.
我們晚上可以這樣來嗎
Ooh, can we do that tonight?
什么  不要
What? No.
好吧  也許恐嚇教育法是很傻
All right, maybe the "Scared straight" thing was a dumb idea.
但是我只是...我想要崔維斯開始
But I just--I want travis to start thinking
思考他的前途
about his future.
我也沒有一畢業就工作
I didn't start working right after college,
但你現在瞧瞧我
and look at me now.
我現在是個又成功又負責的企業家
I'm a successful, responsible business owner.
格雷森  看看這對假貓爪
Grayson, look at these prosthetic cat paws
雪球也能來調酒啦
so Snowball can mix drinks.
我沒有...我都不知道那是啥
I didn't-- what was that about?
我都不知道他在那里
I didn't even know he was back there.
我知道崔維斯的事情我管太多了
I know I meddle in Travis' life.
我是想  我希望他能做個聰明的決定
I just--I want him to make smart choices
那他就不會像鮑比和我那樣糾結
so he doesn't end up struggling like Bobby and I did.
他現在22歲了
Look, he's 22 years old now.
他會去做他想要做的事情
He's gonna do what he wants to do,
如果你教育得當
and if you've raised him right,
那么他已經有判斷的能力了
then he already has the tools to make the right decisions.
而且  我們也知道他很成熟
Besides, we know he's mature.
他整天都跟一群成年人混在一起
I mean, all he does is hang with a bunch of adults.
格雷森  你給雪球做的胡須
Grayson, the mustache you made
跟它的胡子黏不上
won't stick to Snowball's whiskers.
我們需要一些能給貓貓用的膠水
We need a cat-safe adhesive.
你是故意找最尷尬的時候來的吧
Are you trying to time these for maximum embarrassment?
對啊  但是認真說
Yeah. But seriously,
我們要你幫忙貼胡子
we need your help with the whiskers.
艾莉是我大學心理課的助教
Ellie was my psych T.A. in college,
我請教她一些學習問題
so I asked for study help,
她跟我說答疑時間是晚上去她家
and she said office hours were that night at her house.
一瓶龍舌蘭酒之后
Well, bottle of tequila later,
我們就在泡泡浴里纏在一起了
we're all tangled up in a bubble bath.
其他的大家都知道了
The rest is history.
感覺我們的故事
It's like our story was lifted
是從《格言》里寫出來的一樣
straight off the pages of "Maxim" Magazine.
男性雜志
親愛的
Oh, oh, baby.
你是不是該降降溫了  拉女王
Maybe dial it back a notch, L-word.
我不會中途放棄感情的
I don't do relationships halfway.
莫瑞一對在看我們
Quick, the Murray's are looking.
快吻我耳朵  舌頭伸進來
Stick your tongue in my ear. Make it deep.
你到底在哪個路邊小店里
At what roadside truck stop
學會經營這種感情了
did you learn about relationships?
難道我就該坐在這里
I guess I'm supposed to just sit here, unloved,
孤獨地看著你對我不管不問嗎
by a seething ball of negativity.
至少我不是那個欲求不滿的家伙
Well, at least I'm not a giant pit of need.
真不好意思我很急切
I'm sorry that I'm so needy!
你就是個冷冰冰的人  從來都不碰我
You're just a cold fish. You never touch me!
我們在公眾場合
We're at a public event.
不是一個可以耳交和全身按摩的地方
This is not the ideal place for ear sex and a full-body rubdown.
你就是這么理所當然
All you do is take me for granted.
我不停地付出  付出  付出
I give and I give and I give
做一個最好的拉拉
to be the very best lesbian I can,
你卻完全不在乎
and you never care!
我受夠了  你聽到了嗎
I am done. Do you hear me?
受夠了
Done!
不好意思
Excuse me.
我們是愛之深責之切
We fight because we love.
不好意思
Uh, excuse me.
為什么我們的小喵喵穿著夏威夷襯衫
Why is our cat-tender wearing a hawaiian shirt?
因為它是一只潮貓
Oh, because he's a flair cat,
像《雞尾酒》里的湯姆·克魯斯
like Tom Cruise in "Cocktail."
我都不懂貓貓怎么做這些事情
I don't know how cats work with these things.
我們才不要做什么高價的貓貓雞尾酒
We are not doing some cheesy cat-tail rip-off.
雪球是一只黑色電影貓
Snowball is a film noir cat,
它是一只給冷硬的亨弗萊·鮑嘉
Serving up martinis
美國男演演員  借《卡薩布蘭卡》獲得奧斯卡提名
端上馬提尼的那種貓
to hard-boiled Humphrey Bogart types.
誰聽說過什么黑色電影貓
Who's ever heard of a film noir cat?
那誰又聽說過貓貓雞尾酒
Who's ever heard of a "Cocktail" Cat?
我不覺得現在的氣氛適合貓
I don't think this is a healthy cat-mosphere.
這是我的基友日  我想要《貓薩布蘭卡》
This is my bro day, and I wanna do "Cat-sablanca."
這是我的酒吧  我想要《貓貓雞尾酒》
Well, this is my bar, and I wanna do "Cat-tail."
這是我的貓...
This is my cat--
湯姆  閉嘴
Shut up, Tom!
你不能聽這些話
You should not have to listen to this.
非常不專業
Very unprofessional.
崔崔
Hey, Trav.
我收到你短信了 我知道你很生氣
Look, I just got your text. I know you're mad.
坐
Sit.
兒子  我收到你信息了
Okay, son, I got your text,
我也知道你肯定氣炸了
And I know you're pissed off.
-坐下吧  -糟了
- Park it. - Ooh. Shoot.
你們知道嗎  我從船上下來
You know, when I was walking away
往回走的時候  我自己想了想
from the boat earlier, I thought to myself,
除了我爸媽  誰還會想出一個
"Who else but my parents would come up with an idea
恐嚇教育法這么扯的辦法
as stupid as a 'scared straight' routine?"
我們起初還覺得這主意不錯呢
It seemed so smart when we thought of it.
記憶猶新啊
I was impressed with us.
我生氣是因為你們把我當個孩子看
I was mad that you'd treat me like a child,
我覺得我忽視了你們很久
so I figured I'd ignore you for a few days,
所以叫你們來向我道歉
make you come to me and apologize.
但是我這么做好像
But that seemed like the behavior
還是像個孩子
of, well, a child.
所以我得做點大人做的事了
So, thought I'd try something a little more adult.
拜托  兒子
Oh, man.
-你是要打我一拳嗎  -不是  爸
- Am I about to get punched in the face? - No, dad.
我叫你們來是要和你們說謝謝
I brought you here to say thanks.
雖然有的時候
Even though you show it
你們兩個總是做些傻事
in amazingly stupid ways sometimes,
但是我知道你們是關心我的
I know you guys care about me.
我也覺得你們是很好的父母
And I think you guys are great parents.
哦  我滴小寶貝長大了
Oh, my little boy has gotten so dadgum mature.
你這么做顯得我好"成熟"啊
Not really helping the adult vibe, mom.
進去喝點咖啡吧
Let's get in there and grab some coffee.
我覺得事情進展不錯
I think that went okay.
是的  很好
Yes, it did.
所以我這次必須得花錢買咖啡了
I'm so gonna have to pay for these coffees.
是的  沒錯
Yes, you are.
你為什么在臉上畫胡子
Why did you draw whiskers on your face?
我在扮演雪球的吧臺助理
I am playing snowball's bar back.
這叫做盡職盡責
It's called committing.
我希望你扮一個有本事的貓
Well, I hope you can commit to flair cat,
因為那才是咱們忙活的事
'cause that's what we're doing.
快看我  我多厲害
Look at me, I have flair! Oh!
快看我  我是電影里的黑幫大姐
Well, look at me! I'm a film noir rip-off.
她的從爪子到耳朵
Her gams went all the way
都散發著光彩
from her paws to her ears.
一開始我就知道這貓會帶來大麻煩
I could tell from the start that this tabby was trouble.
怎么了  你們倆在干什么
What's happening here? What are you guys doing?
我們兄弟倆在一起聚聚
We're having awesome bro time.
等等  咱么是在休息嗎
Oh, wait. Are we taking a five?
一點都不狂拽酷炫
This isn't bro-dacious at all.
是呀  我想我沒法像之前那么奔放了
Yeah, I guess I can't get as wild as I used to.
能給我一杯酒嗎
Do you think maybe I could get a drink?
我和艾莉分手了
Ellie and I broke up.
真為你難過
Oh, I'm sorry.
愛情走得太快就像龍卷風
She's like a tornado.
不能承受你已無處可躲
She sweeps you up, knocks you down,
雖然這會很疼
and as much as it hurts,
但是你就是想讓她再來一次
you just want her to do it all over again.
你身上一股貓味兒
You smell like cat litter.
我要向你道歉
I wanna apologize.
我知道你就是想幫我
I know you were just trying to help.
對不起  我太入戲了
I'm sorry I got so carried away.
我只是...沒有機會
It's just... I never had a chance
去這么好的學校念書
to go to a great school like that.
我真心希望斯坦能上好學校
And... I really wanted it to work out for Stan.
你能這么關心他  這真好
And it's so sweet that you care about him so much.
我當然關心他
I really do.
如果有把槍指著我的頭
And if there was a truth gun to my head,
我也關心你
I really care about you, too.
我也是
I feel the same.
兄弟  對不起剛才那么混蛋
Man, I'm sorry for being such a jerk.
對不起我剛剛那么...
I'm sorry for being so...
我想說  那么"貓性"
I'm tempted to say "Catty."
千萬別
Don't.
我希望我沒搞砸今天的事
I just wish I hadn't ruined everything today.
對于斯坦來說  那所學校太浮夸了
That school's too pretentious for Stan.
他應該去更好的地方
He deserves better.
不管怎樣  你是個非常棒的女友
And for what it's worth, you were a great girlfriend.
謝謝
Thanks.
你也是個很贊的女友
You were a really good girlfriend, too.
你吻技也很好
And you're a great kisser.
你也不賴呀
You weren't bad, yourself.
謝謝
Thank you.
這里沒有攝像機哦
The camera's not even here.
抱歉我之前在船上那么說你
I'm sorry for what I said about you on the boat.
你一點也不悲催
You're not pathetic.
我只是想讓小崔懂我的意思
I was just trying to get through to Trav.
我明白  茱爾斯
I know, Jules.
我們都是想給他最好的
You know, we both just want what's best for him.
也許他不是總能體會咱們的良苦用心
And we may not get through to him all the time,
但是我們還是做了正確的事
but overall, I'd say we did all right.
歡迎來到新巴克  您要喝什么
Welcome to coffee bucks. Can I take your order?
小崔  你在里面干什么
Trav, what are you doing back there?
圍裙是不是你偷的
Did you steal that apron?
你可惹了大麻煩了
You're gonna get in so much trouble!
兩位  我在這里工作
Guys, I work here now.
我給經理打電話  又面試了一次
I called the manager and asked for a second chance.
所以  兩位來點什么
So... what can I get for ya?
這是我第一天上班
It's my first shift,
我只知道怎么做咖啡
I only know how to make coffee.
兩杯咖啡
Two coffees.
-好嘞  -謝謝
- There you go. - Thank you.
我不打算收你們錢
I'm not supposed to take your money.
不要錢嗎
My coffees are free?
也不是真的免費
Well, they're not exactly free...
這是不是你喝過的最難喝的咖啡
Is this the worst coffee you've ever had?
天  這味道就像水里摻了土
Man, it tastes like dirt and water.
哥們兒  怎么了
Wow. What'll it be, pal?
你認識那邊的那人嗎  那個瘦子
Do you know the mug at the end of the bar? Skinny sal?
喝得多  小費給的還少
Big drinker, bad tipper.
哈哈  喵
Ha ha, meow.
他倒不是看起來那么蠢
He's not as dumb as he looks.
他是個有錢人
He's the top money man for--
他倒不是看起來那么蠢  他是個
He's not as dumb as he looks. He's the top--
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
這爪子太難用了
These paws suck!
挺好的  還幫我抓老鼠
Thoughtfully, help me catch mice.
雪球肯定不會原諒我了
Snowball's never going to forgive me for this.